{
    "questions":[
{
"question":"1.Which of the following statement is correct for AngularJS?",
"choices":["AngularJS is an HTML framework","AngularJS is a Java framework","AngularJS is a JavaScript framework","AngularJS is a SQL framework"],
"correctAnswer":"AngularJS is a JavaScript framework"
},
{
    "question":"2. On which of the Architectural pattern AngularJS is based?",
    "choices":["Observer Pattern","Decorator pattern","MVC Architecture pattern","MVVM Architectural pattern"],
    "correctAnswer":"MVVM Architectural pattern"
},
{
    "question":"3.AngularJS is perfect for?",
    "choices":["SPAs","MPAs","DPAs","CPAs"],
    "correctAnswer":"SPAs"
},
{
    "question":"4.Which of the following is the correct syntax for writing AngularJS expressions?",
    "choices":["(expression)","{{expression}}","{{{expression}}}","[expression]"],
    "correctAnswer":"{{expression}}"
},
{
    "question":"5.Which of the following directive is used to bind the application data to the HTML view in AngularJS?",
    "choices":["ng-bind directive","ng-app directive","ng-model directive","ng-init directive"],
    "correctAnswer":"ng-bind directive"
},
{
    "question":"6.What is the use of Angular Controllers in the application?",
    "choices":["Angular controllers are used for controlling the data.","Angular controllers are used for displaying the data.","Both of the above are correct.","None of the above is correct."],
    "correctAnswer":"None of the above is correct."
},
{
    "question":"7.Which of the following is used to share data between controller and view in AngularJS?",
    "choices":["using Model","using services","using factory","using $scope"],
    "correctAnswer":"using services"
},
{
    "question":"8.Which of the following is not a valid AngularJS filter?",
    "choices":["lowercase","orderby","email","currency"],
    "correctAnswer":"email"
},
{
    "question":"9.Who is known as the father of AngularJS?",
    "choices":["Brad Green","Misko Hevery","Adam Abrons","Mike Adams"],
    "correctAnswer":"Misko Hevery"
},
{
    "question":"10. Which of the following community Angular JS belong to?",
    "choices":["Twitter","Facebook","Google","Microsoft"],
    "correctAnswer":"Google"

}]
}




